<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Emergency App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Emergency App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gtc">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_report">Create Report</string>
    <string name="title_activity_past_reports">Past Reports</string>
    <string name="title_activity_report_detail">Report Details</string>

    <string-array name="menu_array">
        <item>Detail Exchange Guide</item>
        <item>Past Reports</item>
        <item>Emergency Reaction Guide</item>
        <item>FAQs</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Log In</string>

    <string-array name="vehicle_type_array">
        <item>- Select one-</item>
        <item>Type 1</item>
        <item>Type 2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="prompt_vehicle_type">Vehicle Type</string>

    <string-array name="vehicle_brand_array">
        <item>- Select one-</item>
        <item>Audi</item>
        <item>BMW</item>
        <item>Chevrolet</item>
        <item>Chrysler</item>
        <item>Citroen</item>
        <item>Dacia</item>
        <item>Daihatsu</item>
        <item>Dodge</item>
        <item>Ferrari</item>
        <item>Fiat</item>
        <item>Ford</item>
        <item>Honda</item>
        <item>Hyundai</item>
        <item>Jaguar</item>
        <item>Jeep</item>
        <item>KIA</item>
        <item>Lada</item>
        <item>Lamborghini</item>
        <item>Lancia</item>
        <item>Land Rover</item>
        <item>Lexus</item>
        <item>Lotus</item>
        <item>Maserati</item>
        <item>Mazda</item>
        <item>Mercedes</item>
        <item>Mitsubishi</item>
        <item>Nissan</item>
        <item>Opel</item>
        <item>Porsche</item>
        <item>Renault</item>
        <item>Seat</item>
        <item>Smart</item>
        <item>Subaru</item>
        <item>Suzuki</item>
        <item>Toyota</item>
        <item>Vauxhall</item>
        <item>Volkswagen</item>
        <item>Volvo</item>
        <item>other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="emergency_react_guide_motorway_arr">
        <item>\u2022 Pull on to the hard shoulder and stop as far to the left as possible with the wheels turned to the left</item>
        <item>\u2022 Leave your sidelights on and turn on the hazard warning lights get out of the vehicle by the left-hand door and make sure that all your passengers do the same</item>
        <item>\u2022 Leave animals in the vehicle or in an emergency, keep them under proper control on the verge</item>
        <item>\u2022 If you have reflective jackets in the vehicle wear them – do not use a warning triangle on the hard shoulder</item>
        <item>\u2022 Make sure that passengers keep away from the carriageway and hard shoulder and children are kept under control – it is best to retreat up the bank, or behind a barrier if this is possible don\'t attempt even simple repairs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="emergency_react_guide_road_arr">
        <item>\u2022 Once in a safe place use a mobile phone to call the AA, making sure you can describe your location – look out for the new Driver Location Signs which will help us pinpoint your location and direction of travel, or there are reference numbers on all telephones and marker posts.</item>
        <item>\u2022 If you have a smart phone you can download the AA App, which uses the GPS function on the phone to find your exact location. With the simple touch of an icon both the call and the location are transferred to the AA Control Centre.</item>
        <item>\u2022 If you don\'t have a mobile walk to an emergency telephone on your side of the carriageway – never attempt to cross the carriageway. Follow the arrows on the posts at the back of the hard shoulder – the phone is free and connects directly to the police/Highways Agency. Give full details to the police and tell them if you are a vulnerable motorist, such as a woman travelling alone.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="emergency_react_guide_notes_arr">
        <item>\u2022 If you have a smart phone you can download the AA App, which uses the GPS function on the phone to find your exact location. With the simple touch of an icon both the call and the location are transferred to the AA Control Centre.</item>
        <item>\u2022 If you don\'t have a mobile walk to an emergency telephone on your side of the carriageway – never attempt to cross the carriageway. Follow the arrows on the posts at the back of the hard shoulder – the phone is free and connects directly to the police/Highways Agency. Give full details to the police and tell them if you are a vulnerable motorist, such as a woman travelling alone.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="detail_xchg_guide_terms_arr">
        <item>\u2022 A person, other than yourself, is injured</item>
        <item>\u2022 Damage is caused to another vehicle or to someone else\'s property - including street lamps, signs, bollards etc.</item>
        <item>\u2022 An animal* has been killed or injured, except in your own vehicle or trailer </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="detail_xchg_guide_actions_1_arr">
        <item>\u2022 Stop and remain at the scene for a reasonable period</item>
        <item>\u2022 Give your vehicle registration number, your name and address, and that of the vehicle owner (if different) to anyone with reasonable grounds for asking for those details</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="detail_xchg_guide_actions_2_arr">
        <item>\u2022 Produce your certificate of insurance, if anyone at the scene has reasonable grounds to see it.</item>
        <item>\u2022 If you do not, you must report the accident at a police station or to a constable as soon as you can and in any case within 24 hours. You\'ll need to produce your certificate of insurance but if you don\'t have it when reporting the accident to the police, you may take it, within seven days of the accident, to the police station you nominate when you report the incident.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="prompt_vehicle_brand">Vehicle Brand</string>

    <string name="google_app_id">ornate-reef-125513</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail_exchange_guide">DetailExchangeGuide</string>
</resources>
